(Raj:)I'm such a dog.
(Howard:)There you go again.
(Raj:)I'm sorry, have I been
complaining about it too much?
(Howard:)Actually, what you're doing is
pretending to complain,
(Howard:)but really trying to brag.
(Raj:)How could you say that?
(imitates Koothrappali): "Oh,
I wish could enjoy a cup of tea
(Howard:)without a naked girl
bouncing up and down on me."
(Raj:)I never said that.
"Don't you hate it when you
can't remember whose bra it is
you found wedged in your couch?"
(Raj:)Okay, that I said.
But that's a real problem!
(Raj:)You give a girl
another woman's bra,
(Raj:)and you will not be
having sex with her that night.
(Raj:)Maybe the other girl,
but not her.
(Amy:)What's going on with him?
(Penny:)Oh, he's all
bent out of shape
(Penny:)about having
a Roommate Agreement meeting.
(Sheldon:)Apparently, perfect attendance
isn't cool anymore.
(Penny:)Don't worry,
he'll come around.